The only thing they can count on is each other.
Flight of the Intruder is a action, war film directed by John Milius.
Navy pilot Lt.
Jake Grafton and his bombardier buddy, Lt.
Virgil Cole, are two soldiers embedded in the Vietnam War growing
frustrated by the military's constraints on their missions.
Despite the best efforts of their commanding officer, Cmdr.
Frank Camparelli, to re-engage them, this disillusioned pair decide to take the war effort into
their own hands with an explosive battle plan that could well get them court-martialed.
Cmdr. Frank 'Dooke' Camparelli, played by Danny Glover.
Lt. Cmdr. Virgil 'Tiger' Cole, played by Willem Dafoe.
Lt. Jake 'Cool Hand' Grafton, played by Brad Johnson.
Callie Joy, played by Rosanna Arquette.
Boxman, played by Tom Sizemore.
Lt. Cmdr. 'Cowboy' Parker, played by J. Kenneth Campbell.
Flight of the Intruder is a 1991 war film directed by John Milius, and
starring Danny Glover, Willem Dafoe, and Brad Johnson.
It is based on the novel of the same name by former
Grumman A-6 Intruder pilot Stephen Coonts.
The film received negative reviews upon release, and was
Milius's final theatrical release as a director.
The film explores themes of vietnam war, bomber, u.s. navy, aviation, combat.